Finding Aid for the Carol Burnett Papers PASC.0066
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Press Clippings, 1955-2000s; Series 7.; 11 boxes
  - Press clippings: 1960-1969, Subseries 3.; 4 boxes
    - Press clippings, 1969; 1 folder, loose clippings (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, 1969; 1 folder, loose clippings (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, 1969; 1 folder, loose clippings (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, 1969; 1 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, 1969; 1 folder, loose clippings (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Press Clippings: 1970-1979, Subseries 4.; 3 boxes
    This sub-series contains press clippings from 1970-1979 related to Carol Burnett including theater, film and television projects: "Plaza Suite," "I Do! I Do!," "Same Time Next Year," "Pete 'n Tillie," "The Front Page," "The Wedding," "The Carol Burnett Show," "Julie and Carol at Lincoln Center," "Once Upon a Mattress," "Sills and Burnett at the Met," "Dolly and Carol at Nashville," and "Friendly Fire."
    - Allan, Ingersoll and Weber, Public Relations, June 24, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 16)
      Contains original envelope with Allan, Ingersoll and Weber, Public Relations contact information.
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 1)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, Entertainer of the Year Award, Mel Torme television special The Price of Fame.
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, 1970; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings, 1971; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 9)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, fundraising appearances for charity functions, International Radio and TV Society.
    - Press clippings, 1971; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, 1972; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, television broadcast of Once Upon a Mattress (1972), Pete 'n Tillie.
    - Press clippings, 1972; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 2)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, TV broadcast of Once Upon a Mattress (1972), Pete 'n Tillie.
    - Press clippings, 1973; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, Pete 'n Tillie.
    - Press clippings, 1973; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 1974; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 5)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, 6 Rms Riv Vu.
    - Press clippings, 1974; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, 1975; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, 1976; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 9)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, Sills and Burnett at the Met, People's Choice Awards.
    - Press clippings, 1976; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, 1977; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 46, Folder 11)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, Sills and Burnett as the Met, The Wedding, Same Time, Next Year.
    - Press clippings, 1977; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, The Wedding,
    - Press clippings, 1978; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, various charity events and special television appearances.
    - Press clippings, 1979; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Press clippings, 1979; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Press clippings, 1979; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 47, Folder 6)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: the Carol Burnett Show, various charity events and special television appearances; coverage of her daughter, Carrie Hamilton's, drug problem.
    - Press clippings, 1979; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Press clippings, undated [1970s]; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 47, Folder 8)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett.
  - Press clippings 1980-1989, Subseries 5.; 1 boxes
    This sub-series contains press clippings from 1980-1989 related to Carol Burnett including theater, television and film projects: "Same Time, Next Year" (co-starring Burt Reynolds), "Eunice," "The Four Seasons."
    - Press clippings, 1980; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: Same Time, Next Year (with Burt Reynolds), The Four Seasons, the Carol Burnett Show.
    - Press clippings, 1980; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 48, Folder 2)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: Same Time, Next Year with Burt Reynolds, The Four Seasons, the Carol Burnett Show.
    - Press clippings, 1981-1983; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including the television show Eunice.
    - Press release, [1980]; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 12)
      Contains press release regarding Honorary Doctorate of Humane letters from Emerson College awarded to Carol Burnett.
  - Press clippings 1990-1999, Subseries 6.; 1 boxes
    This sub-series contains press clippings from 1990-1999 related to Carol Burnett including film, television and live performances: "From the Top," and "Love Letters."
    - Press clippings, 1990-1996; 1 folder; loose clippings (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Contains press clippings related to Carol Burnett including: Love Letters, From the Top.
  - Press Clippings, Undated; Subseries 7.; 1 boxes
    Content arranged in alphabetical order.
    The sub-series contains undated and unidentified press clippings.
    - Corydon Weekly Democrat, July 14, 1863; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 15)
      Contains copy of newspaper The Corydon Weekly Democrat, Corydon, Indiana.
    - Old Los Angeles Times headlines, undated; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Contains section of Los Angeles Times special edition featuring old headlines. Also contains original envelop addressed to "Mr. J Hamilton 1375 N. Doheny Dr. Los Angeles 69, Calif."
- Scrapbooks, 1956-1991; Series 8.; 1 manuscript box; 8 flat boxes
  This series contains scrapbooks made predominately of press clippings with some photographs related to Carol Burnett. Contents include projects such as: "The Gary Moore Show," "Calamity Jane," "Carol and Company," "Once Upon a Mattress," and the "Carol Burnett Show."
  - Scrapbook, 1956-1963, bulk 1963; 1 folder; loose pages of scrapbook (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Single, loose pages of a scrapbook. Materials include photographs, show programs and press clippings of Carol Burnett on: The Gary Moore Show; Julie and Carol at Carnegie Hall; with Buddy Hackett from show Stanley; Carol and Co. with Robert Preston. Unclear who made scrapbook. Many of the photographs are signed "To Tony, Love Carol." No indication in book who Tony might be.
    1 of 4 folders that make up complete original scrapbook. Pages separated by sheet of acid free paper and are kept in same order they appeared in original binding.
  - Scrapbook, 1956-1963, bulk 1963; 1 folder; loose pages of scrapbook (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Single, loose pages of a scrapbook. Materials include photographs, show programs and press clippings of Carol Burnett on the: Gary Moore Show; Julie and Carol at Carnegie Hall; with Buddy Hackett from show Stanley; Carol and Co. with Robert Preston. Unclear who made scrapbook. Many of the photographs are signed "To Tony, Love Carol." No indication in book who Tony might be.
    2 of 4 folders that make up complete original scrapbook. Pages separated by sheet of acid free paper and are kept in same order they appeared in original binding.
  - Scrapbook, 1956-1963, bulk 1963; 1 folder; loose pages of scrapbook (Box 28, Folder 3)
    3 of 4 folders that make up complete original scrapbook. Pages separated by sheet of acid free paper and are kept in same order they appeared in original binding.
  - Scrapbook, 1956-1963, bulk 1963; 1 folder; loose pages of scrapbook (Box 28, Folder 4)
    4 of 4 folders that make up complete original scrapbook. Pages separated by sheet of acid free paper and are kept in same order they appeared in original binding.
  - Scrapbook, 1957-1960; Black vinyl book, 17 1/2"x19 1/2" (Box 37)
    Scrapbook of press clippings pertaining to Carol Burnett's performance of song I made a Fool of Myself Over John Foster Dulles on the Jack Paar Show (1957); and appearances on the Gary Moore Show. Includes photographs of Burnett with Moore, Joe Hamilton, Dinah Shore, Dick Van Dyke.
  - Scrapbook, 1962-1963; Light brown bound cardboard book, 11"x14" (Box 30)
    Scrapbook in original book and binding; contains newspaper clippings pertaining to general press coverage of Carol Burnett during 1962-1963.
  - Scrapbook, 1963; 1 box,, 12"x17 3/4" (Box 35)
    Scrapbook of newspaper clippings for 1963 that includes press coverage of: Julie and Carol at Carnegie Hall; Burnett leaving the Gary Moore Show; Burnett winning T.V. Guide's Favorite Female Performer, a Peabody and two Emmy Awards.
    Pages separated by sheet of acid free paper and are kept in same order they appeared in original binding.
  - Scrapbook, 1963; Brown vinyl cover, 12"x16" (Box 36)
    Scrapbook in original book and binding (with "Carol Burnett" engraved on cover); contains newspaper clippings pertaining to general press coverage of Carol Burnett during 1963 including television specials Calamity Jane, Carol and Company (co-starring Robert Preston) and feature film Who's Been Sleeping in My Bed.
  - Scrapbook, 1963-1965; Brown vinyl book cover, 12"x15" (Box 31)
    Scrapbook containing materials--newspaper clippings, telegrams, photographs--pertaining to: Fade Out, Fade In; CBS television broadcast of Once Upon a Mattress (1964); photographs of Julie Andrews and Carol Burnett performing at the President's Ball (1965).
    Photos of Fade Out, Fade In located in separate folder 15.19, s.s. 2.2; congratulation telegrams for Fade Out, Fade In located in separate folder 29.4, s.s. 2.2; photos of Andrews and Burnett performing at the President's Ball located in separate folder 15.20, s.s. 2.16.
  - Scrapbook, 1971; 1 folder, loose pages (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Loose pages of scrapbook for 1971. Contains press clippings.
  - Scrapbook, 1972, 1976; Black vinyl book, 24"x20" (Box 38)
    Scrapbook pertaining to Sills and Burnett at the Met special (1976)and Once Upon a Mattress (1972).
  - Scrapbook 1, 1974; 1 folder, loose pages (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Loose pages of scrapbook for 1974. Contains press clippings.
  - Scrapbook 2, 1974; 1 folder, loose pages (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1976; 1 folder, loose pages (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Loose pages of scrapbook for 1976. Contains press clippings related to the Carol Burnett Show and its 10th year anniversary.
  - Photo Album-scrapbook, 1991; 1 folder, loose photo and pages of album (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Includes pages from original three ringed photo album; photographs are loose; cards and program notes are still in clear plastic album sleeves. Materials include: photos of Carol Burnett during 1991 with cast of Love Letters, Julie Andrews, Tim Conway, Lyle Waggoner, Harvey Korman, Walter Matthau; production stills of the Carol Burnett Show (1991) and cards of congratulations to Burnett for the start of the show's season.
- The Carol Burnett Show (Music), Series 9.; unknown
  This series contains musical arrangements that were processed prior to June 2009 and do not have box or folder numbers. See report in the collection file for further information. For additional musical arrangements related to the "Carol Burnett Show" (1966-1978), researchers should see Series 3: Television Projects, Sub-Series 4: "Carol Burnett Show" (1966-1978.)
  Contents arranged in alphabetical order according to title.
  - unspecified, 0424 (Box Unknown container 255 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 420 (Box Unknown container 256 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0316 (Box Unknown container 257 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0424 (Box Unknown container 258 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0019 (Box Unknown container 259 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0316 (Box Unknown container 260 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 261 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0019 (Box Unknown container 262 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0019 (Box Unknown container 263 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0019 (Box Unknown container 264 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0019 (Box Unknown container 265 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0019 (Box Unknown container 266 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 267 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 268 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 269 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 270 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 271 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0507 (Box Unknown container 272 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0507 (Box Unknown container 273 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0010 (Box Unknown container 274 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 275 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 276 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 126 (Box Unknown container 277 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 126 (Box Unknown container 278 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 279 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 280 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 281 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 282 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 283 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 284 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 285 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified (Box Unknown container 286 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 287 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 288 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, 0003 (Box Unknown container 289 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - unspecified, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 290 for instance of, Folder unknown container)
  - 0515, Matz, Peter/Lawrence, Steve/Martin, Dick (Box Unknown container 291 for instance of 0515, Folder unknown container)
  - A. Winter, 710 (Box Unknown container 292 for instance of A. Winter, Folder unknown container)
  - Al Woodbury, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #5 (Box Unknown container 293 for instance of Al Woodbury, Folder unknown container)
  - Al Woodbury, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 294 for instance of Al Woodbury, Folder unknown container)
  - Aquarius (Box Unknown container 295 for instance of Aquarius, Folder unknown container)
  - Artie Butler, None Listed (Box Unknown container 296 for instance of Artie Butler, Folder unknown container)
  - Artie Butler, None Listed (Box Unknown container 297 for instance of Artie Butler, Folder unknown container)
  - Artie Malvin (Box Unknown container 298 for instance of Artie Malvin, Folder unknown container)
  - Bert Clayton Williams, Carol's Solos (Box Unknown container 299 for instance of Bert Clayton Williams, Folder unknown container)
  - Bob Florence, 0114 (Box Unknown container 300 for instance of Bob Florence, Folder unknown container)
  - Carol and Sammy (Box Unknown container 301 for instance of Carol and Sammy, Folder unknown container)
  - Closing Theme ("It's Over! Come Along With Us!") (Box Unknown container 302 for instance of Closing Theme ("It's Over! Come Along With Us!"), Folder unknown container)
    The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6.
  - Dick De Benedictus, Julie and Carol at Lincoln Center (Box Unknown container 303 for instance of Dick De Benedictus, Folder unknown container)
  - Dick De Benidictus, Julie and Carol at Lincoln Center (Box Unknown container 304 for instance of Dick De Benidictus, Folder unknown container)
  - Dick De Benidictus, Julie and Carol at Lincoln Center (Box Unknown container 305 for instance of Dick De Benidictus, Folder unknown container)
  - Dick Grove, 0502 (Box Unknown container 306 for instance of Dick Grove, Folder unknown container)
  - Don Costa (Box Unknown container 307 for instance of Don Costa, Folder unknown container)
  - Don Costa (Box Unknown container 308 for instance of Don Costa, Folder unknown container)
  - Eddy Samuels, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 309 for instance of Eddy Samuels, Folder unknown container)
  - Eddy Samuels, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 310 for instance of Eddy Samuels, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 311 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 312 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 313 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 314 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 315 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 316 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 317 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, Jimmie Rodgers Show No. 2 (Box Unknown container 318 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #5 (Box Unknown container 319 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #5 (Box Unknown container 320 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #5 (Box Unknown container 321 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 322 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 323 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 324 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 325 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #5 (Box Unknown container 326 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 327 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 328 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 329 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 330 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 331 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #6 (Box Unknown container 332 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 333 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 334 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 335 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 336 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Frank Comstock, The Jimmy Rodgers Show #4 (Box Unknown container 337 for instance of Frank Comstock, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0323 (Box Unknown container 338 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0323 (Box Unknown container 339 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0323 (Box Unknown container 340 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0323 (Box Unknown container 341 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0322 (Box Unknown container 342 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0410 (Box Unknown container 343 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0322 (Box Unknown container 344 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Miscellaneous Box 2 (Box Unknown container 345 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Carol + 2 (Box Unknown container 346 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Carol + 2 (Box Unknown container 347 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0410 (Box Unknown container 348 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Miscellaneous Box 2 (Box Unknown container 349 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0316 (Box Unknown container 350 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, Carol + 2 (Box Unknown container 351 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0411 (Box Unknown container 352 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0411 (Box Unknown container 353 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)
  - Harry Zimmerman, 0411 (Box Unknown container 354 for instance of Harry Zimmerman, Folder unknown container)